thiswentviral.net 2018-09-22

# Privacy Policy

  * __[ HOME](http://thiswentviral.net/ "HOME")
  * Privacy Policy

YTSSubtitles.com ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to in our terms of use and this policy) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting YTSSubtitles.com you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

### Information We May Collect From You

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information you give us. You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site YTSSubtitles.com or by corresponding with us by e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you subscribe to our service, search for a product, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our site, enter a competition, promotion or survey, and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and in some cases phone number.
  * Information we collect about you. With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information:
  *     * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, operating system, platform.
    * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.
  * This information does not, however, identify you by name, and it is not necessary for you to provide us with your name or address to use our site.

### Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, including our affiliate companies.

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.
  * Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information that identifies you by name or provides your address to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in London). We may make use of the data we have collected from you that does not identify you by name to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Well Known Media Limited, our customers, or others.

### Links to third party Websites:

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check this page frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

### Contact

We value your ideas and thoughts about YTSSubtitles.com, we rely on our users to help us make the site better. If you have any thoughts, problems or suggestions then contact us Here
